ncbuy.com 2016-02-08

# NCBuy: Service Center - Privacy Policy

|  | 

Your privacy is important to both of us, and we keep your details confidential. Mum's the Word!   
  
---|---  
  
NCBuy Privacy Statement

NetCent Communications, the owner of this Web site, has created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following documentation discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

DATA AND INFORMATION SHARING  
When information is shared with third parties on an _aggregate basis_ , said third parties can not link this information to any one specific person. This is broad demographic information. For example, a third party may know that a certain percentage of visitors to this Web site are women, but they do not know who these women are.

Any data or personally identifiable information collected by this site may be shared with third parties at any time, on a broad, _aggregate basis only_ , unless specifically noted otherwise and with user consent.

The site owner reserves the right to disclose member information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the site owner's rights or property, other visitors, members, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. The site owner also reserves the right to disclose visitor or member information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

USER CONFIRMATION REQUIREMENTS  
All newsletter subscription or membership offers made by this Web site require followup confirmation by the user.

Not only must the user specifically request to join a service (such as an email newsletter subscription list), but that request must also be confirmed with a followup action. After the initial request is received by our systems, a message is sent to the email address that was submitted to notify the user that we have received a request to join one of our services. This request is considered to be in a pending state and is not processed until the user clicks on a link within the email message to actually confirm that they did indeed make the request. If the user does not click on the confirmation link within the time allowed, the pending request is automatically deleted.

Although this process does require an additional step on the part of the user, we have always taken this approach to maintain the integrity of our systems and to prevent one user from subscribing another user without their consent.

COMPUTER INFORMATION  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to maintain system and data security, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information.

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to allow you to maintain your preferences for this Web site. We do not share the contents of cookies that we set with any third party.

Using normal Web server logs, we keep track of the types of Web browsers that users are accessing our site with. This information is used to determine which types of browser-specific services we should be launching. This information is not tied to any personal data.

REGISTRATION FORMS  
Our site's registration forms require users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). This information is used to contact you, when necessary, to answer your questions, provide support, or to deliver the services that you have specifically requested. Demographic and profile data collected by this site is considered personal and confidential and is not shared with third parties on an individual basis without your prior consent.

ORDER FORMS  
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders to our customers. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. We do not share information regarding customer buying patterns.

SWEEPSTAKES AND GIVEAWAYS  
We run sweepstakes and giveaways on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address), demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level) and their opinions on survey questions and topics. We use this contact information to select and notify winners. Responses to survey and opinion questions are used solely on an aggregate basis and are not made available to any third parties.

BANNER AND TEXT ADVERTISEMENTS  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site - including Google, which utilizes the DoubleClick DART cookie. These companies may use information ( ** _not_ including your name, address, email address, or telephone number**) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).  

  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on Web content you visit at this or other Web sites. To learn more about Google's privacy or to opt-out of using the DoubleClick DART cookie, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

THIRD PARTY MEMBERSHIP OFFERS  
From time to time we may make membership offers for third party sites or services available to our visitors through the use of a pull down selection or checkbox that is integrated into our existing forms. When a visitor to our site completes one of these forms and chooses to accept one of the provided membership offers, contact information submitted by the user will be sent to the third party identified on the form for the sole purpose of processing that request.

  * MyView, a service of _Authentic Response_ , is a private research community governed by a strict [privacy policy](http://portal.myview.com/portal/app?cmd=TextPage&_ppId=21) that allows members to receive opportunities to take part in paid and unpaid surveys from today's leading businesses. 

THIRD PARTY EMAIL SUBSCRIPTIONS  
Through registration forms on this site, we provide users with the opportunity to subscribe to news and announcement email list topics that are managed with the Authentic Response system, under a strict **double opt-in policy.** When you submit a request to subscribe to one of these list topics, the information that you provide is sent to Authentic Response to process your request. Before your request can be finalized, an email will be sent to the email address provided requesting your approval. Authentic Response's strict data privacy and protection policy is certified by the Trust Guard system, and can be [verified at any time](https://secure.trust-guard.com/certificates/www.authenticresponse.com) online.

PUBLIC CHAT, MESSAGE BOARDS, AND BLOGS  
If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by NetCent Communications. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other such sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.

SITE SECURITY  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

HAVE A QUESTION, COMMENT, OR SUGGESTION?  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact the privacy administrator online using the site's [contact and support form](http://www.ncbuy.com/servicecenter/contacts.html), or through regular postal mail at:

ATTN: Privacy Administrator  
NetCent Communications  
157 Harwood Avenue North, Suite 226  
Ajax, Ontario L1Z 0B6
